You can't cheat death twice.
The Jester 2 is a horror, thriller, crime film directed by Colin Krawchuk.
When teen magician Max crosses paths with the sinister Jester on Halloween night, she must outsmart a
supernatural killer whose magic is all too real and whose tricks always end up in blood.
The Jester, played by Michael Sheffield.
Max, played by Kaitlyn Trentham.
Willie, played by Dingani Beza.
Logan, played by Hassen Kacem.
Mom, played by Jessica Ambuehl.
Diner Patron, played by Charles Mckee.
A jester, also known as joker, court jester, or fool, was a member of the household of
a nobleman or a monarch kept to entertain guests at the royal court.
Jesters were also travelling performers who entertained common folk at fairs and town markets, and the
discipline continues into the modern day, where jesters perform at historical-themed events.
Jester-like figures were common throughout the world, including
Ancient Rome, China, Persia, and the Aztec Empire.
During the post-classical and Renaissance eras, jesters are often thought to have
worn brightly coloured clothes and eccentric hats in a motley pattern.
Jesters entertained with a wide variety of skills: principal among them were song, music, and storytelling, but many also
employed acrobatics, juggling, telling jokes (such as puns and imitation), and performing magic tricks.
Much of the entertainment was performed in a comic style.
Many jesters made contemporary jokes in word or song about
people or events well known to their audiences.
The tone is dark and intense.